An hour and a haIf of beach houses...
(Leonard:)...until the woman turns around
and realizes love was here all along.
(Penny:)Come on, that is a great movie.
And it starts in ten minutes.
But I hate those movies.
- No, you don't.
- Yes, I do.
(Leonard:)The only reason I went is because you
wanted to see them and I wanted sex.
(Leonard:)To this day I can't see
a Sandra Bullock poster...
(Leonard:)...without getting both bored
and aroused.
(Penny:)So while we were going out,
how often would you pretend...
(Penny:)...to like things
just to have sex with me?
(Leonard:)All the time.
(Penny:)You're kidding.
(Leonard:)Does this sound familiar?
"l'd love to go
shoe shopping with you."
"Hiking, it's great."
"It's 2 a.m., of course,
I wanna go to Koreatown...
(Leonard:)...and sing karaoke with your friends.
Who wouldn't?"
(Penny:)Okay. We were going out.
You were gonna get sex anyway.
Really? You would've slept with me after
a three hour documentary on dams?